[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress played the part of Carrie White in the movie \u201cCarrie\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Sissy Spacek", "incorrect_answers": ["Betty Buckley", "Amy Irving", "Piper Laurie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The carbon atom in amino acids has four elements/groups attached to it in all amino acids (except for proline). Which of the following is not among these four?", "correct_answer": "Methyl group", "incorrect_answers": ["Carboxyl group", "R-group (including another hydrogen)", "Hydrogen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "6 is a multiple of 2 and 3, 9 is a multiple of 3 only, 10 is a multiple of 5 and what other number?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "15", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What alloy contains copper and zinc, with a content of copper typically more than 50%?", "correct_answer": "Brass", "incorrect_answers": ["Rutite", "Bronze", "Stainless Steel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many stripes are on the American Flag?", "correct_answer": "13", "incorrect_answers": ["11", "15", "12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brocas area is located in the human brain. What is it responsible for?", "correct_answer": "Speech", "incorrect_answers": ["Hearing", "Sleep patterns", "Eyesight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The human heart is about the size of a fist.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the title of an 80s song by Duran Duran: \nNew Moon on...", "correct_answer": "... Monday", "incorrect_answers": ["... See ya soon!", "... Thursday", "... Friday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you studied petrology, where would your interests lie?", "correct_answer": "rocks", "incorrect_answers": ["petroleum", "microbes", "veins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This villain from a 1989 movie is at # 45 in the American Film Institute\u2019s list of the 50 most memorable movie villains.", "correct_answer": "The Joker", "incorrect_answers": ["Venom", "Lex Luther", "The Riddler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is an output device that produces audible sound?", "correct_answer": "Speaker", "incorrect_answers": ["Printer", "Microphone", "Monitor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sympathy for the Devil is a song, originally released by this British rock band.", "correct_answer": "The Rolling Stones", "incorrect_answers": ["Black Sabbath", "Queen", "Sex Pistols"]}]